Guide to the American Federation of Television and Radio Artists (AFTRA), New York Local Records WAG.282
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: Administrative Files
  - Groot, Kenneth: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Groot, Kenneth: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1983-1985 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Groot, Kenneth: NY State Department of Labor Correspondence, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Groot, Kenneth: Correspondence, Re: British Information Services, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Groot, Kenneth: Correspondence, Re: Cassette Casting Incorporated, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Groot, Kenneth: Correspondence, Re: CETA Funds, 1975-1979 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Groot, Kenneth: Correspondence, Re: Claman, Barbara Associates, 1971-1972 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Groot, Kenneth: Correspondence, Re: Communications Act, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Groot, Kenneth: Correspondence, Re: Sarnow, Alma Talent Payment Service, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Groot, Kenneth: NY State Department of Labor Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Groot, Kenneth: US Government Correspondence, 1971-1986 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Hall, John: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Hall, John: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Hall, John: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Hall, John: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Hall, John: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Hall, John: Correspondence, Re: Immigration, 1978-1980 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Handbook, 1950 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Handbook, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Handbook: Chicago Local, 1945 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Handbook: Drafts and Correspondence, 1950-1967 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Handbook: Los Angeles Local, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Handbook: New York Local, 1945 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Handbook: New York Local, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Handbook: San Francisco Local, 1946 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Heller, George Foundation: Memorial Foundation Committee, 1977-1985 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Heller, George Foundation: General, 1959-1965 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Heller, George Foundation: General, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Heller, George Foundation: General, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Heller, George Foundation: General, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Heller, George Foundation: Scholarships, 1977-1988 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Heller, George Foundation: Tow Path Art Show And Related Materials, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Henderson, Althea: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1984-1985 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Inter-American Federation of Entertainment Workers: Journal, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - International Broadcasters Society: Printed Materials, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - International Labor Press Association: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1965-1966 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - International Labor Press Association: Printed Materials, 1964-1966 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - International Secretariat of Entertainment Trade Unions: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - J.P. Stevens Boycott, 1976-1977 (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - J.P. Stevens Boycott, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - J.P. Stevens Boycott, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Legal: Becker and London Correspondence, 1967-1980 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Legal: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Legal: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Legal: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Legal: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Legal: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1977-1980 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Legal: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1981-1983 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Legal: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Legal: General, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Legal: Pre-Paid Fees, 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Lewis, Irving: Christmas Card lists, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence and Related Materials, Jan-Jul 1967 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence and Related Correspondence, Aug-Dec 1967 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence and Related Materials, Jan-Jul 1968 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence and Related Materials, Aug-Dec 1968 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Jan 1972 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence and Related Materials, Feb-Mar 1972 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Apr-May 1972 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence and Related Materials, Jun-Jul 1972 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Aug 1972 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence and Related Materials, Sep-Oct 1972 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence and Related Materials, Nov-Dec 1972 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence and Related Materials, Jan-Mar 1973 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence and Related Materials, Apr-Jun 1973 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence and Related Materials, Jul-Sep 1973 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence and Related Materials, Oct-Dec 1973 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Jan 1974 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence and Related Materials, Feb 1974 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Mar 1974 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence and Related Materials, Apr 1974 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence and Related Materials, May 1974 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Jun-Jul 1974 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence and Related Materials, Aug 1974 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Sep 1974 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Oct 1974 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence and Related Materials, Nov-Dec 1974 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence and Related Materials, Jan-Feb 1975 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence and Related Materials, Mar 1975 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence and Related Materials, Apr 1975 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, May 1975 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence and Related Materials, Jun-Jul 1975 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Aug 1975 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence and Related Materials, Sep 1975 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence and Related Materials, Oct-Dec 1975 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence and Related Materials, Jan-Mar 1976 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence and Related Materials, Apr-Jun 1976 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Jul 1976 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence and Related Materials, Aug-Sep 1976 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Oct-Nov 1976 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence and Related Materials, Dec 1976 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Jan 1977 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence and Related Materials, Feb-Mar 1977 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Apr 1977 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence and Related Materials, May-Jun 1977 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Jul 1977 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence and Related Materials, Aug-Sep 1977 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence and Related Materials, Oct-Dec 1977 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Jan 1978 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence and Related Materials, Feb-Mar 1978 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Apr-May 1978 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence and Related Materials, Jun-Jul 1978 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Aug 1978 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence and Related Materials, Sep 1978 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Oct 1978 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence and Related Materials, Nov-Dec 1978 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Jan 1979 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Feb 1979 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Mar 1979 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Apr 1979 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, May 1979 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Jun 1979 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Jul 1979 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Aug 1979 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Sep 1979 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Oct 1979 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Nov 1979 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Dec 1979 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Jan 1980 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Feb 1980 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Mar 1980 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Apr 1980 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, May 1980 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Jun 1980 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Jul 1980 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Aug-Sep 1980 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Oct 1980 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Nov-Dec 1980 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Jan-Feb 1981 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Mar 1981 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Apr 1981 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, May 1981 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Jun 1981 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Jul 1981 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Aug-Sep 1981 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Oct-Nov 1981 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Dec 1981 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Jan 1982 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Feb-Mar 1982 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Apr 1982 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, May 1952 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Jun 1982 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Jul 1982 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Aug 1982 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Sep 1982 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Oct 1982 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Re: AFL-CIO, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Re: Hash Berry Productions, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Lewis, Irving: Correspondence, Labor, Re: Reform Bill, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Lewis, Irving: New York Chapter Industrial Relations, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Local: Boston, Correspondence and Related Materials, 1979-1981 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Local: Chicago, Correspondence and Related Materials, 1974-1981 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Local: Cleveland, Correspondence and Related Materials, 1967-1969 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Local: Cleveland, Correspondence and Related Materials, 1976-1982 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Local: Detroit, Correspondence and Related Materials, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Local: Los Angeles, Correspondence and Related Materials, 1961-1965 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Local: Los Angeles, Correspondence and Related Materials, 1966-1969 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Local: Los Angeles, Correspondence and Related Materials, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Local: Los Angeles, Correspondence and Related Materials, 1971-1972 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Local: Los Angeles, Correspondence and Related Materials, 1973-1974 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Local: Los Angeles, Correspondence and Related Materials, 1975-1976 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Local: Los Angeles, Correspondence and Related Materials, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Local: Los Angeles, Correspondence and Related Materials, 1978-1979 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Local: Los Angeles, Correspondence and Related Materials, 1980-1982 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Local: Kansas City, Correspondence and Related Materials, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Local: Kansas City, Correspondence and Related Materials, 1979-1982 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Local: Philadelphia, Correspondence and Related Materials, 1966-1981 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Local: Pittsburgh, Correspondence and Related Materials, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Local: San Francisco, Correspondence and Related Materials, 1965-1975 (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Local: San Francisco, Correspondence and Related Materials, 1979-1983 (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Local: Seattle, Correspondence and Related Materials, 1979-1980 (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Local: Washington-Baltimore, Correspondence and Related Materials, 1964-1969 (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Local: Washington-Baltimore, Correspondence and Related Materials, 1970-1980 (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Local: Washington-Baltimore, Correspondence and Related Materials, 1981-1983 (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - Membership Activities Committee: Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - Membership Mailings, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - Membership Mailings, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - Membership Mailings, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 49)
  - Membership Mailings, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 50)
  - Membership Mailings, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 51)
  - Membership Mailings, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 52)
  - Membership Mailings, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 53)
  - Membership Mailings, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 54)
  - Membership Mailings, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 55)
  - Membership Mailings, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 56)
  - Membership Mailings, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 57)
  - Membership Mailings, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 58)
  - Membership Mailings, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 59)
  - Membership Mailings, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Membership Mailings, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Membership Mailings, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Membership Mailings, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Membership Mailings, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Membership Mailings, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Membership Mailings, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Membership Mailings, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Membership Mailings, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Membership Meetings: Prizes, 1987-1988 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Members Working For Non-Signatories, 1970-1974 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Minneapolis Local: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Miss America Pageant, 1971-1980 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Miss Universe: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1972-1985 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Moore, Dick: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1974-1976 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Moore, Dick: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1977-1979 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Mr. Mike's Mondo Video, 1979-1980 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Mrs. America Pageant, 1978-1979 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - National Association of Educational Broadcasters: Journal (Article about AFTRA), 1965 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - National Education Television: "Sesame Street" Correspondence, 1970-1972 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - National Public Radio (NPR): Correspondence, 1977-1982 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - NBC Incorporated: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1965-1966 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - New Member Orientation: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1980-1988 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - New York City Central Labor Council, 1979-1981 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - New York State Department of Labor: Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - New York State Motion Picture and Television Advisory Board: Astoria Motion Picture and Television Center, 1976-1981 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - New York State Motion Picture and Television Advisory Board: Astoria Studio, Board Meeting Minutes, 1978-1980 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - New York State Motion Picture and Television Advisory Board: Astoria Studio, Progress Reports, 1978-1980 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - New York State Motion Picture and Television Advisory Board: Committees, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - New York State Motion Picture and Television Advisory Board: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1978-1979 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - New York State University, 1964-1965 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Non-Communist Affidavits, 1952 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Non-Communist Affidavits, 1953 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Non-Communist Affidavits, 1954 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Non-Communist Affidavits, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Non-Communist Affidavits, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Non-Communist Affidavits, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Non-Communist Affidavits, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Non-Communist Affidavits, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - Non-Communist Affidavits, 1961 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - Non-Communist Affidavits, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - Non-Communist Affidavits, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - Non-Communist Affidavits, Jan-May 1964 (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - Non-Communist Affidavits, Sep-Nov 1964 (Box 24, Folder 45)
  - Office of Film, Theatre, and Broadcasting: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1975-1979 (Box 24, Folder 46)
  - Office of Film, Theatre, and Broadcasting: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1980-1983 (Box 24, Folder 47)
  - Office of Film, Theatre, and Broadcasting: Nancy Littlefield, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 48)
  - Officers: Beck, Jackson, 1973-1977 (Box 24, Folder 49)
  - Officers: Greenhouse, Martha, 1977-1981 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Officers: Harvey, Kenneth, 1969-1979 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Officers: Marcus, Dianne, 1983-1987 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Officers: Marcus, Dianne, Jan-Mar 1985 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Officers: Marcus, Dianne, Apr-Dec 1985 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Officers: Marcus, Dianne, 1987-1988 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Officers: Marshall, Rex, 1963-1965 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Officers: Reed, Carol, 1965-1966 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Officers: Roberts, Kenneth, 1968-1969 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Office and Professional Employees International Union (OPEIU): Correspondence and Related Materials, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - OPEIU: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - OPEIU: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - OPEIU: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - OPEIU: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - OPEIU: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - OPEIU: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - OPEIU: Negotiations, 1972-1974 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - OPEIU: Negotiations, 1975-1978 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - OPEIU: Negotiations, 1981-1984 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Open Door Committee: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1987-1989 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Organizing: WSNL-TV, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Overseas TV Reports, 1967-1970 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Parade: Labor Day, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Parade: Labor Day, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Parade: Labor Day, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Parade: Labor Pride, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Parade: Macy's Thanksgiving, 1982-1984 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Parade: Macy's Thanksgiving, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Parade: Macy's Thanksgiving, 1985-1988 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Pension and Welfare: Amended Retirement Benefits Plan, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Pension and Welfare: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1965-1966 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Pension and Welfare: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1967-1969 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Pension and Welfare: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1970-1976 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Pension and Welfare: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1977-1980 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Pension and Welfare: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1981-1983 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Pension and Welfare: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Pension and Welfare: Committee, 1980-1987 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Pension and Welfare: Health Services Plan, undated (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Pension and Welfare: Jersey Standard Club Optical Plan, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Pension and Welfare: National Optical Plan, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Pension and Welfare: Previn, Dory and United Artists Records Correspondence, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - Pension and Welfare: Printed Materials, 1956-1965 (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - Pension and Welfare: Reports, 1970-1976 (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - Pension and Welfare: Reports, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - Pension and Welfare: Unioncare Personal Benefits Programs, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - Pension and Welfare: Unioncare Personal Benefits Programs, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 46)
  - Pension and Welfare: Unioncare Personal Benefits Program, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 47)
  - Performer's Seminar Committee: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 48)
  - Poole, Roy: "Directions", 1976 (Box 25, Folder 49)
  - Press: Comic Strips, 1960s (Box 25, Folder 50)
  - Press: Obituaries, 1963-1968 (Box 25, Folder 51)
  - Press: Press Releases and Related Materials, 1954-1958 (Box 25, Folder 52)
  - Press: Press Releases and Related Materials, 1959-1962 (Box 25, Folder 53)
  - Press: Press Releases and Related Materials, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 54)
  - Press: Press Releases and Related Materials, Jan-Jul 1965 (Box 25, Folder 55)
  - Press: Press Releases and Related Materials, Aug 1965 (Box 25, Folder 56)
  - Press: Press Releases and Related Materials, Sep-Dec 1965 (Box 25, Folder 57)
  - Press: Press Releases and Related Materials, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Press: Press Releases and Related Materials, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Press: Press Releases and Related Materials, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Press: Los Angeles Local AFTRA, 1965-1966 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Rage, Andy: WICC, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Read Files, Aug-Dec 1974 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Read Files, Jan-Apr 1975 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Read Files, May-Jul 1975 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Read Files, Aug-Dec 1975 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Read Files, Jan-Feb 1976 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Read Files, Mar-May 1976 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Read Files, Jun-Aug 1976 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Read Files, Sep-Dec 1976 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Read Files, Jan-Apr 1977 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Read Files, May-Aug 1977 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Read Files, Sep-Dec 1977 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Read Files, Jan-Mar 1978 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Read Files, Apr-May 1978 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Read Files, Jun-Sep 1978 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Read Files, Oct-Dec 1978 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Read Files, Feb 1984 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Read Files, Mar-Apr 1984 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Read Files, May-Jun 1984 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Read Files, Jul 1984 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Read Files, Aug 1984 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Read Files, Sep 1984 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Read Files, Oct 1984 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Read Files, Nov-Dec 1984 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Read Files, Jan 1985 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Read Files, Feb 1985 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Read Files, Mar 1985 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Read Files, Apr-May 1985 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Read Files, Jun-Jul 1985 (Box 26, Folder 33)